A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1996-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Clemency: Pardon Files-Denied, 1996-2006 (accessions 42418, 42513 and 42630) RESTRICTED FOR 75 YEARS., Extent: 21.76 cu. ft. (Box 31-87, 285-287)
  - Subseries C: Denials, 2003-2006 (accessions 42418 and 42513).
    - Compton, Sammy W. (26 August 2003) (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Taylor, Darryl Thomas (26 August 2003) - See Also Box 49 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Arrington, Daniel Vincent, denied 3 September 2003 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Caudill, Boliver, denied 3 September 2003 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Chaffin, Timothy Scott, denied 3 September 2003 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Clay, Robert, denied 3 September 2003 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Dubose, Frank L., denied 3 September 2003 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Galderisi, Joanne P., denied 3 September 2003 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Hutcherson, Lynn R., denied 3 September 2003 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Jones, Clarence Wendell, denied 3 September 2003 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Raia, Louis William, denied 3 September 2003 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Simons, Carl Gene, denied 3 September 2003 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Kerry Lee, denied 3 September 2003 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Carter, Joan Elizabeth, denied 17 October 2003 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Goins, Kenneth, denied 17 October 2003 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Jackson, Virginia, denied 17 October 2003 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Lakisha R., denied 17 October 2003 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Whitley, Caprice L., denied 17 October 2003 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Burns, Steven McLorey, denied 13 November 2003 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Compton, Sammy W., denied 13 November 2003 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Dodson, Randall Daniel, denied 13 November 2003 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Harper, Jeanette Gay, denied 13 November 2003 (part one) (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Harper, Jeanette Gay, denied 13 November 2003 (part two) (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Harper, Jeanette Gay, denied 13 November 2003 (part three) (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Hightower, David, denied 13 November 2003 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Levi, Timothy J., denied 13 November 2003 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Payne, Clarence Lee Wilbur, denied 13 November 2003 - See Also Box 47 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Sykes, Titus, denied 13 November 2003 - See Also Box 47 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Taylor, Darryl Thomas, denied 13 November 2003 - See Also Box 47 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Torabipour, Hassan, denied 13 November 2003 - See Also Box 39 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - White, David Eugene, denied 13 November 2003 - See Also Box 47 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Whitworth, Linda, denied 13 November 2003 - See Also Box 39 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Arnett, Greg (17 December 2003) - See Also Box 53 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Baker, Paul (17 December 2003) - See Also Box 53 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Barnes, John Monroe (17 December 2003) - See Also Box 53 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Bryant, Kenneth N. (17 December 2003) - See Also Box 53 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Ward, Christopher Damond (17 December 2003) - See Also Box 53 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Yannello, Angelina (17 December 2003) - See Also Box 53 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Reedy, Davey James (30 January 2003) (part one) - See Also Box 57 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Reedy, Davey James (30 January 2003) (part two) (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Reedy, Davey James (30 January 2003) (part three) (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Reedy, Davey James (30 January 2003) (part four) (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Reedy, Davey James (30 January 2003) (part five) (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Ledford, Michael (2003 and 2004) (part one) - See Also Box 55 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Ledford, Michael (2003 and 2004) (part two) (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Ledford, Michael (2003 and 2004) (part three) (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Ledford, Michael (2003 and 2004) (part four) (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Ledford, Michael (2003 and 2004) (part five) (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Ledford, Michael (2003 and 2004) (part six) (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Price, Anthony, denied 11 January 2002 (videotape) - See Also Box 37 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Hare, Jamie, denied 22 May 2003 (videotape) - See Also Boxes 43 and 44 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Williams, Gary M. (undated) (videotape) (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Simms, Sr., Lawrence Hugh (20 January 2004) (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Foltz, Sr., Festus B., denied 28 January 2004 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Graves, Dennis Ray, denied 28 January 2004 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Wenger, Geoffrey Eugene, denied 28 January 2004 - See Also Box 39 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Arnett, Greg, denied 24 February 2004 - See Also Box 49 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Atkins, William Todd, denied 24 February 2004 - See Also Box 47 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Baker, Paul, denied 24 February 2004 - See Also Box 49 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Barnes, John Monroe, denied 24 February 2004 - See Also Box 50 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Bryant, Kenneth N., denied 24 February 2004 - See Also Box 50 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Forney, Costella L., denied 24 February 2004 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Long, Jason Douglas, denied 24 February 2004 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Thomas, Jr., Carl Anthony, denied 24 February 2004 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Wallace, Kenneth Francis, denied 24 February 2004 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Yannello, Angelina, denied 24 February 2004 - See Also Box 50 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Edmonds, Henry T., denied 26 February 2004 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Evans, Thomas R., denied 26 February 2004 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Barrilleaux, Roland J. (26 February 2004) (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Lafferty, Larry S. (26 February 2004) (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Rollins, Terry (26 February 2004) - See Box 37 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Ward, Christopher Damond, denied 26 February 2004 - See Also Box 50 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Hassan, Mohammad, denied 9 March 2004 - See Also Box 45 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Jain, Kusum, denied 9 March 2004 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - McKenzie, Bradley, denied 9 March 2004 - See Also Box 45 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Ray, David Ernest, denied 9 March 2004 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Samuel, III, Douglas L., denied 9 March 2004 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Frizzell, Laura Joyce, denied 10 March 2004 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Anderson, Davon Antonio, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Berryhill, Jr., Calvin E., denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Carter, Douglas, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Goss, Kevin Leroy, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Harper, Diane, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Henderson, Thomas Roy, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Hernandez, Jaime R., denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Hill, Keith L., denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Johnson, Bernard, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Johnson, Lorenzo, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Johnson, Michael, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - King, Jr., Wister, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Lipscomb, David Bryan, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Maitner, Jr., Robert E., denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Martin, Bradley Steven, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Martin, Christopher W., denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Merritt, Joseph, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Mitchell, Danny, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Murphy, Mark, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Palmer, Tamara, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Philpott, Michael M., denied 7 May 2004 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Scott, Cynthia B., denied 7 May 2004 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Smalls, Jr., Douglas, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Andrew L., denied 7 May 2004 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Stonelake, Christopher, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Weiss, Jr., Josef Gene, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - White, Tyron, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Wiggins, Joshua, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Williams, Victoria, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, Burnette Renee, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Muhammad, Medad El, denied 10 May 2004 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Antalan, Brigitte J., denied 21 July 2004 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Hylton, Mark Keith, denied 21 July 2004 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Ledford, Michael, denied 21 July 2004 - See Also Box 51 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Mullins, Randal, denied 21 July 2004 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Whitney, Jacqueline, denied 21 July 2004 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Amen-Ra, Menelik A., denied 30 August 2004 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Booker, Sarita Michelle, denied 30 August 2004 (part one) (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Booker, Sarita Michelle, denied 30 August 2004 (part two) (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Cooper, Aaron, denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Courtney, Harry B., denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Day, Donald Wayne, denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Dearing, Jr., Alfred Lovell, denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Edmonds, Lewis Lyn, denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Flores, Marcelino Rubio, denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Gordon, Deshena, denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Hankins, Jeffrey Carrol, denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Jackson, Michael Paul, denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Kay, James P., denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Kornegay, Nahshon, denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - LaSala, Debra, denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Malone, Alicia M., denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - McLean, Quentin, denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Nelson, Tyrone, denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Newman, Herman C., denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Pitt, Jr., Anthony J., denied 30 August 2004 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Shaddock, Frederick, denied 30 August 2004 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Jr., Daniel F., denied 30 August 2004 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - White, Aaron D., denied 30 August 2004 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Zorumski, Sr., Joseph Kevin, denied 30 August 2004 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Drayton, Theodore, denied 8 September 2004 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Fragala, Michael A., denied 8 September 2004 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Marron, Travis J., denied 9 September 2004 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Maulick, Richard S., denied 9 September 2004 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Reedy, Davey James, denied 9 September 2004 - See Also Box 50 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Reedy, Davey James, denied 9 September 2004 (cassette tapes) (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Williams, Joseph Donald, denied 9 September 2004 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Basnight, Dex Irwin Elijah, denied 15 September 2004 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Bradshaw, William Lee, denied 1 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Brown, Ronald Jeffrey, denied 1 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Bynum, Ray Leonard, denied 1 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Contreras-Avelar, Ernesto, denied 1 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Cox, Ronald E., denied 1 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Dix, Matthew Aaron, denied 1 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Hairston, Jeffrey M., denied 1 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Hayslett, James Randolph, denied 1 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Hodnett, Lafayette Scott, denied 1 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Liverman, Michael Antonio, denied 1 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Mohabir, Sharmalee, denied 1 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Monahan, Michael Turner, denied 1 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Naleppa, Nicholas (Nick), denied 1 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Turner, Michael Forrest, denied 1 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Dean, Carolyn M. (Medical Clemency Request), denied 13 December 2004 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Aghaji, Virginia, denied 2 December 2005 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Agyemang, Linda S., denied 11 January 2006 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Argabright, Bobby (Medical Clemency Request), denied 23 May 2005 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Andrews, Paulette, denied 16 January 2006 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Ashby, Jeffrey Allen, denied 29 June 2005 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Bagby, John Jackson, denied 8 November 2005 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Bailey, Michael Anthony, denied 2 December 2005 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Bain, Michael Craig, denied 8 November 2005 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Barksdale, Jr., Melvin, denied 7 April 2005 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Barnes, Zenas J., denied 14 July 2005 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Bates, George Albert, denied 25 January 2005 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Bellner, James W., denied 15 June 2005 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Beskin, Jeffrey S., denied 16 January 2006 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Blevins, Jacob Glen (Medical Clemency Request), denied 16 September 2005 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Boles, Regina, denied 3 May 2005 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Bouzid, Jamal Eddine, denied 26 January 2005 (part one) (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Bouzid, Jamal Eddine, denied 26 January 2005 (part two) (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Bouzid, Jamal Eddine, denied 26 January 2005 (part three) (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Bouzid, Jamal Eddine, denied 26 January 2005 (part four) (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Bouzid, Jamal Eddine (Restoration of Rights, granted 9 January 2003) (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Bray, Jr., Ollie Pete, denied 14 September 2005 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Britt, Jeffrey R., denied 25 January 2005 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Brondas, Beth, denied 25 January 2005 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Brown, Barry, denied 14 July 2005 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Brown, Denise Renee, denied 7 April 2005 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Ernest Lee, denied 2 December 2005 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Blankenship, Johnny R. (2005) (Box 60A, Folder 1)
    - Brown, James Martin, denied 15 March 2005 (part one) (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Brown, James Martin, denied 15 March 2005 (part two) (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Brown, Kimberly A., denied 11 January 2006 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Brown, Leonard, denied 14 July 2005 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Brown, Pamela, denied 29 June 2005 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Brown, Richard Paul, denied 11 February 2005 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Brown, Travis S., denied 13 May 2005 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Brunson, Eleanor (Medical Clemency Request), denied 6 June 2005 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Busch, Richard Joseph, denied 14 September 2005 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Bush, Tonya Taylor, denied 3 May 2005 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Butler, Rebecca Lynn, denied 29 June 2005 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Byrd, Keith Douglas, denied 8 November 2005 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Carter, Carletta T., denied 26 January 2005 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Carter, Jeffrey A., denied 8 November 2005 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Carter, Tyrone Lee, denied 7 April 2005 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Chaires (Colfelt), Carol A., denied 16 January 2006 (part one) (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Chaires (Colfelt), Carol A., denied 16 January 2006 (part two) (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Chaires (Colfelt), Carol A., denied 16 January 2006 (part three) (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Chandler, Derek M., denied 29 June 2005 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Cheatham, Leon, denied 14 July 2005 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Childress, Joseph L., denied 8 November 2005 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Chilton, Adrian L., denied 11 January 2006 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Ciba, Peter Charles, denied 16 January 2006 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Cloud, Braden W., denied 16 January 2006 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Coffey, Jr., Terry L., denied 13 May 2005 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Coles-Gray, Michelynne D., denied 8 November 2005 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Collier, Robert L., denied 25 January 2005 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Collier, Tremel T., denied 8 November 2005 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Collins, Jr., William T. (4 November 2005) (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Cox, Daniel T., denied 2 December 2005 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Crawford-Daniels, Ollin R., denied 28 November 2005 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Cropper, Alex D., denied 8 November 2005 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Davis, Robert Todd, denied 13 May 2005 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - DeCorte, Jason Lee, denied 7 April 2005 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Denny, William Elbert, denied 2 December 2005 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - DeShano, Mark Joseph, denied 2 December 2005 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Dickson, Carole Anne, denied 16 January 2006 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - DiGiovanni-Joyce, Carla, denied 8 November 2005 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Dixon, Ruby L., denied 8 November 2005 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Duncan, Terry Dale, denied 29 June 2005 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Durney, Richard, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Ely, Lisa Lynn, denied 14 July 2005 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Evans, Iris, denied 29 June 2005 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Farmer, Glen L., denied 14 July 2005 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Feigley, Drew B., denied 11 February 2005 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Fernando, Jr., Jose R., denied 16 January 2006 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Ferrall, Anne Marie, denied 16 January 2006 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Finney, David Cecil, denied 14 July 2005 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Fleetwood, Paul Lewis, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Fleischman, Virginia T., denied 14 September 2005 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Flores, Marcelino Rubio, denied 14 September 2005 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Flournoy, Paul Phillip, denied 14 September 2005 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Fox, Naomi L., denied 7 April 2005 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Funchess, Valerie, denied 8 November 2005 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Gadway, Michael S., denied 16 September 2005 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Garner, Jennifer LaRue, denied 2 December 2005 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Gerring, Walter John, denied 7 April 2005 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Goins, Alicia Heather, denied 2 December 2005 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Gordon, Sr., Willie J., denied 14 July 2005 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Graham, Stewart E., denied 16 January 2006 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Grant, Michelle, denied 8 November 2006 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Gregory, III, Liniel G., denied 26 January 2005 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Ham, Jr., Raleigh G., denied 8 November 2005 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Hansard, Rita E. (2005) (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Harlow, Daniel Allen (Medical Clemency Request), denied 29 July 2005 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Hartman, Daniel, denied 29 June 2005 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Hawkins, Leonard J., denied 14 July 2005 (part one) (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Hawkins, Leonard J., denied 14 July 2005 (part two) (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Hawkins, Leonard J., denied 14 July 2005 (part three) (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Hendricks, Clifford E., denied 8 November 2005 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Henry, Horace, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Hinton, Warren, denied 8 November 2005 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Hodges, Keysean, denied 3 May 2005 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Hodges, Linda Sue, denied 8 November 2005 (part one) (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Hodges, Linda Sue, denied 8 November 2005 (part two) (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Hodges, Linda Sue, denied 8 November 2005 (part three) (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Hoskie, Yvettrise Marquitta, denied 13 September 2005 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Howard, Carlos, denied 17 June 2005 (Box 66, Folder 2a)
    - Hubbard, Christopher Dean, denied 11 February 2005 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Huff, Johnny R. (Medical Clemency Request), denied 17 June 2005 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Humphrey, Michael Danny, denied 2 December 2005 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Jenkins, Keith A., denied 11 February 2005 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Johnson, Kevin Troy, denied 25 January 2005 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Jones, Barry Dale, denied 8 November 2005 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Jordan, Malcolm Augustus, denied 11 February 2005 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Jordan, Rock (aka Omar Ali Almomani), denied 14 September 2005 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Kidwell, Terry Francis, denied 11 January 2006 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - King, Damany, denied 21 July 2005 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Knight, Candance, denied 13 May 2005 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Knight, David Leon, denied 13 September 2005 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Krewson, Mark C., denied 13 May 2005 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Lampel, Jason, denied 29 June 2005 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Landry, Jorrick, denied 11 January 2006 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Leach, Veronica W. (2005) (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Lee, Jerry David, denied 14 July 2005 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Leftwich, Kenneth H., denied 7 April 2005 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - LeGrand, Sharon, denied 13 May 2005 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Lewis, Donald William, denied 3 May 2005 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Lloyd, Ethelwyn Vonzetta, denied 14 July 2005 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Lockhard, Robert K. (Medical Clemency Request), denied 11 May 2005 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Lohmeyer, Blair E., denied 28 November 2005 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Lucas, Thomas, denied 11 February 2005 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Ludwig, Rebecca, denied 14 September 2005 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Luttrell, Robert Mitchell, denied 25 January 2005 (part one) (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Luttrell, Robert Mitchell, denied 25 January 2005 (part two) (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Luttrell, Robert Mitchell, denied 25 January 2005 (part three) (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - MacDonald, Alan, denied 2 December 2005 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Martelino, Jr., Jose A., denied 6 January 2006 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Mason, Clarice Odessa, denied 2 December 2005 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Mason, Colbert, denied 11 February 2005 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Matheny, Jr., William T., denied 6 January 2006 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Matthews, Valerie Lee, denied 6 January 2006 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - McCabe, Jr., Thomas J., denied 7 September 2005 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - McDavid, Winifred Buman (2005) (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - McGaha, Crystal Littlestar, denied 29 June 2005 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - McLaughlin, Bruce (2005) (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - McLean, Mary Ellen, denied 2 December 2005 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Melara, Manuel, denied 14 July 2005 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Metzger, John Robert, denied 11 January 2006 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Middleton, Jeremy M., denied 8 November 2005 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Miles, Samuel A., denied 8 November 2005 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Mitchell, Diane Marie, denied 26 January 2005 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Moore, Jr., Saul, denied 3 May 2005 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Moore, Jr., Troy, denied 26 January 2005 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Morgan, Gwendolyn, denied 11 February 2005 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Morse, Donald R., denied 29 June 2005 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Muhammad, Medad El (2005) (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Mullins, Jerettia June, denied 17 June 2005 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Murphy, James D. denied 25 January 2005 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Myers, Kelly Ferrell, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Nguyen, Phillip Minh, denied 8 November 2005 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Noorishad, Mehri Parniani, denied 11 January 2006 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Norris, Elizabeth A., denied 2 December 2005 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - O'Brien, Mi Choong, denied 25 January 2005 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Ojo, Babtunde, denied 2 December 2005 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Oliver, Calvin Thomas, denied 2 December 2005 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Oliver, Dan, denied 14 September 2005 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Opoku-Edusei, Justicia, denied 16 January 2006 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Owens, Jamie Leo, denied 8 November 2005 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Panozo, Johnny Augusto, denied 26 January 2005 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Pare, Jacques, denied 11 January 2006 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Payne, Clarence Lee, denied 14 September 2005 (part one) (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Payne, Clarence Lee, denied 14 September 2005 (part two) (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Payne, John Andrew, denied 8 November 2005 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Payne, Sr., Joseph Patrick, denied 2 December 2005 (Box 70, Folder 9)